export const firstRound = {
  topic: 'Regular Verbs',
  level: 'Intermediate',
  totalQuestions: 10,
  perQuestionScore: 2,
  questions: [
    {
      question:
        'Yesterday, I __ something nice!',
      choices: ['code', 'codes', 'coded', 'have coded'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'coded',
    },
    {
      question:
        'I don\'t __ to work today',
      choices: ['wanted', 'want', 'have wanted', 'wants'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'want',
    },
    {
      question:
        'What was it you __ yesterday? It was delicious.',
      choices: ['cook', 'have cooked', 'had cooked', 'cooked'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'cooked',
    },
    {
      question:
        'I never __ to this!',
      choices: ['agreed', 'have liked', 'has agreed', 'liked'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'agreed',
    },
    {
      question:
        'What __ you __ about?',
      choices: ['did/laughed', 'have/laugh', 'are/laughing', 'do/laughed'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'are/laughing',
    },
    {
      question:
        'Don\'t __ to this song, it will get stuck in your head forever.',
      choices: ['listened', 'listen', 'listens', 'have listened'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'listen',
    },
    {
      question:
        '__ you ever __ at a techno party before?',
      choices: ['have/danced', 'has/danced', 'did/danced', 'are/dancing'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'have/danced',
    },
    {
      question:
        'I __ for five minutes non stop, they are so funny!',
      choices: ['am laughing', 'do laugh', 'have been laughing', 'is laughing'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'have been laughing',
    },
    {
      question:
        'I __ I were taller.',
      choices: ['have wish', 'wish', 'am wishing', 'has wished'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'wish',
    },
    {
      question:
        'Last year, I __ along the Hudson river with my friends.',
      choices: ['was walking', 'walk', 'walks', 'walked'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'walked',
    },
  ],
}